("BACK THAT THANG UP"
BY JUVENILE)
♪♪♪
HEY, HEY.
♪ CASH MONEY RECORDS TAKIN'
OVER FOR THE '99 AND THE 2000. ♪
♪ GIRL YOU WORKIN WITH SOME BACK
YEAH, YOU BACK YEAH ♪
♪ MAKE A BROTHA SPEND HIS CASH
YEAH, HIS LAST YEAH ♪
♪ GIRLS FROWN WHEN YOU PASS
YEAH, THEY MAD YEAH ♪
♪ YOU GON' RIDE IN THE JAG YEAH,
WITH THAT HEAD ♪
♪ YOU COULD SMOKE OR BUY A BAG
YEAH, OF GRASS YEAH ♪
♪ GOT MONEY I CAN FLASH YEAH,
AND TRASH YEAH ♪
♪ I'MA BIG TYMER PLAYA YEAH,
GUN SPREADER YEAH ♪
♪ A PLAYA HATA FLIPPER YEAH,
GRAVE FILLA YEAH ♪
♪ I BE SLANGIN WOOD YEAH,
I'M OUT THE HOOD YEAH ♪
♪ LET IT BE UNDERSTOOD YEAH,
IT'S ALL GOOD YEAH ♪
♪ GOT A PLAYA SCHEMIN' LARGE
YEAH, ON THE HARD YEAH ♪
♪ A SMOOTH LITTLE BROAD YEAH
FROM OUT THE PROJECTS ♪
♪ A HATER DO A TRICK YEAH,
ON THE STICK YEAH ♪
♪ YOU CLAIMIN' YOU WANT
A PICTURE, THAT AIN'T IT YEAH ♪
♪ I'M THE DADDY WITH THE MONEY
YEAH, DON'T ACT FUNNY YEAH ♪
♪ GOT BIRDS AND I'M RUNNIN'
YEAH, BOUT A HUNDRED YEAH ♪
♪ GIRL, YOU LOOK GOOD,
WON'T YOU BACK THAT THANG UP ♪
♪ YOU'S A BIG FINE WOMAN,
♪ CALL ME BIG DADDY
WHEN YOU BACK THAT THANG UP ♪
♪ GIRL, WHO IS YOU
PLAYIN' WITH? ♪
♪ BACK THAT THANG UP ♪
♪ GIRL, YOU LOOK GOOD,
WON'T YOU BACK THAT THANG UP ♪
♪ YOU'S A BIG FINE WOMAN,
♪ CALL ME BIG DADDY
WHEN YOU BACK THAT THANG UP ♪
♪ GIRL, WHO IS YOU
PLAYIN' WITH? ♪
♪ BACK THAT THANG UP ♪
♪ GIRL, YOU LOOK GOOD,
WON'T YOU BACK THAT THANG UP ♪
♪ YOU'S A BIG FINE WOMAN,
♪ YOU GOT A STUPID BACK YEAH,
MAKE ME LAUGH YEAH ♪
♪ MAKE A PLAYA WANNA GRAB THAT,
AUTOGRAPH THAT ♪
♪ I'M SWEATIN' IN THE DRAWERS
YEAH, HARD AND LONG YEAH ♪
♪ WANNA WALK IT LIKE A DOG YEAH,
BREAK YOU OFF YEAH ♪
♪ GET MINE, YOU GON' GET YOURS
YEAH, THAT FOR SURE YEAH ♪
♪ YOU'RE MESSIN' WITH MY NERVES
YEAH AND TO THE CURB YEAH ♪
♪ I KNOW YOU WOMEN KNOW YEAH,
AND IT SHOW YEAH ♪
♪ BUT THE JUVE GOT THE LOW YEAH,
I'M OUT TO FLOW YEAH ♪
♪ FRESH BROUGHT THE BEACH YEAH,
FOR THE SCREECH YEAH ♪
♪ WE BE MAKING HIT YEAH
AFTER HIT YEAH ♪
♪ THEM CHINS SITTIN' NICE YEAH,
I WANNA BITE YEAH ♪
♪ I COULD HIT YOU RIGHT YEAH,
ALL NIGHT YEAH ♪
♪ WANNA TAKE IT TO MY HOUSE
YEAH, ON THE COUCH YEAH ♪
♪ KNOCK THE OUT YEAH,
GET THEM OUT YEAH ♪
♪ I WANNA SEE THE SHOW YEAH,
BEND IT LOW YEAH ♪
♪ LET ME RUN IT IN THE HOLE
YEAH, AND LET ME KNOW YEAH ♪
♪ GIRL, YOU LOOK GOOD,
WON'T YOU BACK THAT THANG UP ♪
♪ YOU'S A BIG FINE WOMAN,
♪ CALL ME BIG DADDY
WHEN YOU BACK THAT THANG UP ♪
♪ GIRL, WHO IS YOU
PLAYIN' WITH? ♪
♪ BACK THAT THANG UP ♪
♪ GIRL, YOU LOOK GOOD,
WON'T YOU BACK THAT THANG UP ♪
♪ YOU'S A BIG FINE WOMAN,
♪ CALL ME BIG DADDY
WHEN YOU BACK THAT THANG UP ♪
♪ GIRL, WHO IS YOU
PLAYIN' WITH? ♪
♪ BACK THAT THANG UP ♪
♪ I KNOW YOU CAN'T STAND IT,
STICK BANDIT ♪
♪ DONE LANDED,
SEE YOUR DRAWERS HANDED ♪
♪ KITTY GON' GET IT Y'ALL,
GAME SPIT AT Y'ALL ♪
♪ PUT THE BROAD ON THE WALL
THEN I HIT IT Y'ALL ♪
♪ LOOKIN' KIND OF LONELY,
I'M FEELIN HORNY ♪
♪ PUT THE PIECE IN THE MIDDLE
LIKE MONIE ♪
♪ BIG-HIPPED PLUMBER CHICK,
AND A HUMMER CHICK ♪
♪ BEAT THE WHAT LIKE A
BRRRRR DRUMMER CHICK ♪
♪ SEE DAT PUDDY-CAT? ♪
♪ LOOK AT DAT ♪
♪ I LOVE WHEN THEY A HOODIE-RAT,
THAT'S A FACT ♪
♪ YOU'S A BIG FINE GET IT GIRL,
QUIT IT GIRL ♪
♪ I'M THE BROTHA, THE BROTHA,
BROTHA, THAT HIT IT GIRL ♪
♪♪♪
♪ GIRL, YOU LOOK GOOD,
WON'T YOU BACK THAT THANG UP ♪
♪ YOU'S A BIG FINE WOMAN,
♪ CALL ME BIG DADDY
WHEN YOU BACK THAT THANG UP ♪
♪ GIRL, WHO IS YOU
PLAYIN' WITH? ♪
♪ BACK THAT THANG UP ♪
♪ GIRL, YOU LOOK GOOD,
WON'T YOU BACK THAT THANG UP ♪
♪ YOU'S A BIG FINE WOMAN,
♪ CALL ME BIG DADDY
WHEN YOU BACK THAT THANG UP ♪
♪ GIRL, WHO IS YOU
PLAYIN WITH? ♪
♪ BACK THAT THANG UP ♪
♪ AFTER YOU BACK IT UP,
THEN STOP ♪
♪ THEN WHA-WHA-WHAT,
DROP DROP IT LIKE IT'S HOT ♪
♪ NOW AFTER YOU BACK IT UP,
THEN STOP ♪
♪ NOW, WHA-WHA-WHA-WHAT
DROP IT LIKE IT'S HOT ♪
♪ NOW DROP IT LIKE IT'S HOT,
DROP DROP IT LIKE IT'S HOT ♪
♪ C-M-B MAKE YOU DROP IT
LIKE IT'S HOT ♪
♪ DROP IT LIKE IT'S HOT,
DROP DROP IT LIKE IT'S HOT ♪
♪ THEY GOTTA WOBBLETY WOBBLETY
WA WA WOBBLETY WOBBLETY ♪
♪ WA WA WOBBLETY WOBBLETY,
DROP DROP IT LIKE IT'S HOT ♪
♪ WOBBLETY WOBBLETY,
WA WA WOBBLETY WOBBLETY ♪
♪ WOBBLETY WOBBLETY ♪